We will start this exercise with the 3 -to -1 method.
Find a comfortable position.
Close your eyes.
Take a deep breath.
And while exhaling, mentally repeat and visualize the number 3
three times and relax your body completely.
take another deep breath and while exhaling mentally repeat and
visualize the number two three times and relax your mind by
thinking of tranquil and and passive scenes.
Take another deep breath and while exhaling mentally repeat and
visualize the number one three times you are now at level one
a deeper healthier level of mind to help you enter a deeper
healthier level of mind I'm going to count from ten to one
on each descending number you will feel yourself going deeper
and you will enter a deeper healthier level of mind 10 9
feel going deeper 8 7 6 deeper and deeper 5 4 3
deeper and and deeper, two, one.
You are now at a deeper, healthier level of mind,
deeper than before.
It is a wonderful feeling to be deeply relaxed,
a very healthy state of being.
We will now program effective sensory projection for your
success.
We will establish subjective points of reference at the animate
matter kingdom with reproductive intelligence and an awareness
of existence.
That is, we will program points of reference in the human body
and mind kingdom at its different levels and different depths as
we study the human anatomy from a psychic point of view.
At this time bring to mind a relative, a friend, or a
person whose face you can remember with the least effort.
We will refer to this person as the subject.
Now I am going to count from 10 to 1 so that
you can attune yourself subjectively to this subject. 10, 9, 8,
7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1. one now recall the subject's
face
at the count of three you will project the subject onto your
mental screen one two
three the subject is now on your mental screen
Now mentally move the subject away from the mental screen so
that the screen can be used as the background.
The color of the screen is black.
Now mentally turn the subjects body so its left side is toward
you.
Now turn the subjects back toward you now turn the subjects
right side toward you now turn the subject to be facing you
notice how the body of the subject stands out against a black
screen.
The screen will now change to red.
The screen is now red.
Notice how your subject stands out against the red screen.
The screen will now change to green the screen is now green
notice how your subject stands out against a green screen the
screen will now change to blue the screen is now blue notice
how your subject stands out against a blue screen.
The color of the screen will now change back to green, back
to red, now back to black.
At the count of three you You will mentally bring your subject
close enough to touch.
1, 2,
3.
The subject is now close enough to touch.
At the count of 3, you will objectively extend your arms and
place your hands, one on each side of the head. 1, 2,
3.
Objectively, place your hands, one on each side of the subject's
head, your right hand over the left ear, and your left hand
over the subject's right ear.
Now study your subject's face, the facial features, the hair,
eyes, eyebrows, nose, nose, cheeks, the character of the face.
Whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension,
you can use as a point of reference in the future.
Now concentrate on your subject's forehead, and at the count of
three, we will enter the bone structure level within the human
kingdom. them one two three desire to detect through
visualization or imagination bone bring back a memory of bone
its shape color and appearance now concentrate on the skull of
your subject and study it from several angles from the left from
the back and from the right whatever you perceive with your
imagination at this dimension you can use as a point of
reference in the future now again concentrate your attention on
your subjects forehead area and at the count of three we will
enter the brain structure level one two three 3.
Desire to detect, through visualization or imagination, a brain.
Recall your previous experience of how a brain looks.
Perhaps you have seen pictures of a brain.
Study the brain from several angles. 4. Desire to detect the
various colors, such as gray in the front,
pink in the mid part and dark red in the back part.
Whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension
you can use as points of reference in the future.
When there is brain damage you may get an impression of black
areas or spots.
To help in the solution of this problem Erase the dark area
or spot and form and project an impression of a healthy brain,
and it is so.
When you imagine a damaged area, get further impressions of the
connecting nerves, which you can then follow to the possible
corresponding malfunctions of the body.
Damaged nerves may impress you as being oval and flat and dark
in color.
Healthy nerves may appear transparent and roundish. Some nerves,
like those in the sensory motor system, cross over from one side
of the brain to the opposite side of the body.
Concentrate your attention on the front part of the brain again
at the count of three we will return to the bone structure
level one two three get an impression of a skull at the
count of three we will return to the outer level one two
three we are now at the outer level get an impression of
the hair the face the eyes and eyebrows to test the senses
you can imagine that you are superimposing the subjects head
over your own as though you were putting on a helmet then
you will test your own senses and whatever you feel reflects a
condition of your subject while your subject's head is
superimposed over your own you can ask what kind of problem your
subject has you may ask whether it is psychological or
physiological and
then clear your mind for a moment of time whatever impression
comes to you immediately after this will tell you the problem of
your subject you will then concentrate in this particular area.
Whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension
you can use as a point of reference in the future.
Remember whenever you put the subject's head over your own to
remove it when you have completed your investigation.
Now raise the body still still facing you, and place your hands
on each side of the ribcage.
Begin concentrating on the center of the chest.
At the count of three, we will again enter the bone structure
level within the human kingdom.
One, two, three. 3. You are now at the bone structure level.
Desire to detect through visualization or imagination
the skeletal structure of your subject.
The ribcage, the spinal column, the arms and legs, and the hip
bones.
We are now able to detect abnormalities at this level and, in
the case of arthritis for example, you may detect a powdery
substance collecting on the joints of the fingers and sometimes
the wrists, elbows, shoulder joints, and even the spinal column.
The same substance will be evident in other joints where
arthritis may occur.
You will also be able to detect fractures old and new. To
determine when a fracture took place, use your time mechanism
device and go back in time until the perceived fracture
disappears and you know then when the fracture occurred.
Whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension
you can use as a point of reference in the future.
Now again concentrate on the center of the chest and at the
count of three we will enter the heart tissue level within the
human Kingdom one two three we are now at the heart tissue
level desire to detect through visualization or imagination your
subjects heart recall previous impressions and pictures of a
heart and recall how it operates imagine this heart which
belongs to your subject imagine it from an external point of
view sense it know it is there feel it whatever you perceive
with your imagination at this dimension you can use as a point
of reference in the future at the count of three the heart
will become transparent one two three the heart is now
transparent imagine how the valves function sometimes you will
get the impression of an enlarged heart or erratic beating or
scar tissue formations and in some cases malfunctioning valves
whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension
you can use as a point of reference in the future to
test for blood pressure. Fold the fingers of your hand around an
artery near the heart. Use your imagination to feel the
intensity of the pulsations.
If you get an impression of strong pulsations, there's high
blood pressure. The strength of pulsations can also indicate
normal or weak pulsations or pressure.
If you get the impression that the artery gives and contracts
that it is flexible, then there is no hardening of the arteries.
An impression of no flexibility means hardening of the the
arteries.
To test for blood chemistry, mentally draw a sample of the
subject's blood and put it in an imaginary test tube.
Then agitate the blood sample and before stopping, decide the
purpose of the test.
Once you have decided to test for the percentage of white blood
cells or sugar content or cholesterol or foreign chemicals. Stop
agitating the sample.
Let it settle.
You will detect two different colors of blood chemistry. The
less dominant color will indicate the substance you are testing
for.
Once you have detected what you are testing for. You will
mentally ask yourself whether you are impressed with high, low,
or normal content. Then clear your mind for a moment and the
first impression you receive is usually the strongest and the
right one. You can repeat this operation with the same blood
sample for the rest of the test.
Whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension,
you can use as a point of reference in the future.
At the count of three, we will enter the lung tissue level
within the human kingdom. One, two, three.
Desire to detect through visualization or imagination two lungs
as they expand and contract.
One lung could be a little larger than the other. This is
sometimes normal.
You may become aware of occasional lung problems, such as fluid
at the bottom of the lungs, or of more serious conditions, such
as infections, tumors, perforations, loss of elasticity,
spasticity, asthma, and other detectable states.
Whatever you perceive with your imagination, you can use as a
point of reference in the future.
Sometimes, portion of a lung or the complete lung have to be
removed through surgery.
When this happens, you will detect a lighter color on the
portion of the lung that has been removed. Or the complete lung,
when removed, may be lighter any portion of the body that has
been amputated will impress you as being lighter in color than
the rest of the body once you have found a malfunctioning part
of the body
sense it changing back to proper functioning and let this be
your final impression
at the count of three we will enter the stomach tissue level
within the human kingdom
One, two, three.
Desire to detect through visualization or imagination your
subject's stomach.
Recall your previous experience for an accurate impression of a
stomach.
Whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension,
you can use as a point of reference in the future.
Some of the more common problems of the stomach are ulcers,
tumors obstructions and the improper balance of gastric juices
in the case of surgery when a portion of the stomach has
been removed you will get an impression of an entire stomach
with the missing parts sensed in a lighter shade or color that
contrast with the rest of the stomach at the of three we
will enter the level to sense the intestinal tract one two three
desire to detect through visualization or imagination the
intestinal tract as it begins at the outlet of the stomach the
first part is a small intestine some of the problems of the
intestines are much the the same as those of the stomach, and
many of these same problems carry over to the large intestine at
the lower right side of the trunk of the body, where the
appendix is located.
Whatever you perceive with your imagination, you can use as a
point of reference in the future.
At the count of three, we will concentrate on the pancreas at
that particular tissue level one two three desire to detect
through visualization or imagination the pancreas it is slightly
below and behind the stomach it is an elongated gland that feeds
its digestive juices through a duct into the small intestines an
obstructed duct could prevent the enzymes from entering the
small intestine.
The pancreas contains islands of cells that produce a hormone
called insulin that is released directly into the bloodstream.
An impression of black spots or islands on the pancreas could
indicate diabetes.
Light spots or islands on the pancreas could indicate
hypoglycemia. Whatever you perceive with your imagination at
this dimension, you can use as a point of reference in the
future.
A final impression of a properly functioning and healthy
pancreas is recommended for better health.
At the count of three, we will enter the liver tissue level
within the human kingdom. One, two, three. 3.
Desire to detect, through visualization or imagination, the
liver.
The liver is a little higher than the pancreas and to the
right in a person's body. It has been said by psychics that
if the liver gives a shiny impression, it is healthy.
If dull, a problem may exist.
There could be one of several things wrong. there could be an
enlargement of the liver tumors or infections whatever you
perceive with your imagination at this dimension you can use as
a point of reference in the future at the count of three
we will enter the gallbladder level within the human kingdom one
two three desire to detect through through visualization or
imagination, the gallbladder.
The gallbladder is attached to the liver. It has a duct that
joins a pancreatic duct to form a common duct into the small
intestine.
Stone formations could exist in any duct of any gland.
When you perceive an impression of stone formations in the
gallbladder or in any duct, Imagine going through the process of
crushing the stones into a fine powder with your fingers and
imagine the powder dissolving in the gland secretions.
Your last impression of the gallbladder should be a healthy one
with no stone formations.
Whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension,
you can use as a point of reference in the future.
Now at the count of three, we will enter the kidney tissue
level within the human kingdom. One, two, three.
Desire to detect, through visualization or imagination, two
kidneys.
You have seen pictures of kidneys before.
Get an impression of them as being solid from an outer point
of view. you.
Sometimes one kidney is a little larger than the other, and
sometimes one is a little higher than the other, but this could
be a normal condition.
Whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension,
you can use as a point of reference in the future. At
the count of three, we will perceive the kidneys being
transparent.
One, two, three.
Desire to sense the kidneys transparent.
If you detect these filtering systems as processing unequally or
differently from each other,
then something could be wrong, such as an infection. An
infection could travel up from the bladder to the kidney or from
the kidney to the bladder. Stone formations also could hinder
the functioning of a kidney.
When this is a case imagine crushing the stone formations into a
fine powder with your fingers and imagine the powder dissolving
in the urine.
Whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension
you can use as a point of reference in the future.
When you get an impression that both kidneys are not functioning
quite well but you're not sure why, then compare the subjects
kidneys to those of a healthy person who has no kidney problems.
The final impression should always be one of health.
At the count of three we will go back to the gallbladder
level 1 2 3 to the liver level to the pancreas level
to the intestinal tract level to the stomach level to the lung
level to the heart level to the skeletal body level now back
to the outer level we are now at the outer level of
the human kingdom here you can study the outer skin by desiring
to perceive it through visualization or imagination you can
detect skin problems such as infections allergies tumors
injuries or scars whatever you perceive with your imagination at
this dimension you can use as a point of reference in the
future now project your subject back in front of the screen
mentally turn the subjects body so the subjects left side faces
you
now turn the subjects back toward you now the right side now
allow the subject to face you change the color of the screen
to red change the color of the screen to green now change
the color to blue the color of the screen will now Now
change back to green, back to red, back to black.
Now imagine your subject in perfect health.
Now cause your subject to disappear from the scene.
Your subject has now disappeared from the scene.
whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension
you can use as points of reference in the future it is
now an accomplished fact that you have established subjective
points of reference in the animate matter kingdom having
reproductive intelligence and an awareness of existence and you
understand how these points of reference apply to the human body
and mind kingdom at its different levels and different depths to
function at these levels and to use these points of reference
all you need is a sincere desire to solve problems your mind
will automatically seek out these points of reference where you
will perceive and become aware of information you can use to
solve problems and this is so in a moment I'm going to
count from 1 to 5 and cause a sound with my fingers
at that moment you will open your eyes be wide awake feeling
fine and in perfect health feeling better than before one
two coming out slowly now three at the count of five you
will open your eyes be wide awake feeling fine and in perfect
health feeling better than before feeling the way you feel when
you have slept the right amount of revitalizing refreshing
relaxing healthy sleep for five eyes open wide awake feeling
fine and in perfect health feeling better than before
to guarantee success with your silver techniques we recommend
that you take take the Silva Seminars live. For more information
over course schedules and locations, log on to silvamethod .com
or call 1 -800 -545 -6463 within the continental United States
or 956 -722 -6391.